A Guide to the Papers of Stanley Clay Walker
Special Collections and University Archives, J. Douglas and Patricia W. Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Virginia State Crime Commission 1966 to 1992
  - Data 1967 to 1991
    - Corrections Study 1972-1973 (Box-folder 57:12)
    - Corrections Study 1973 (Box-folder 57:13)
    - Corrections Study 1973-1974 (Box-folder 58:1)
    - Crime-Reports 1967-1969 (Box-folder 58:2)
    - Criminals, Detection, and Apprehension 1972-1973 (Box-folder 58:3)
    - Evaluation of the Division of Investigation 1979 (Box-folder 58:4)
    - F.B.I. National Academy Association Meeting, August 15, 1969- Virginia State Crime Commission Report by Stanley C. Walker August 15, 1969 (Box-folder 58:5)
    - Financial Data 1972-1973 (Box-folder 58:6)
    - Law Enforcement Administration-Budget 1970-1972 (Box-folder 58:7)
    - Law Enforcement Study-Officer’s Salaries-HJR 98 1972 (Box-folder 58:8)
    - Law Enforcement Study-Division of Justice and Crime Prevention 1972 (Box-folder 58:9)
    - Law Enforcement Officers Training Standards Commission-Budgets, Rules, etc. undated (Box-folder 58:10)
    - Law Enforcement Officers Study, 1973 Session (SJR 79) 1973 (Box-folder 58:11)
    - Organizational Data undated (Box-folder 58:12)
    - Report of Bland Correctional Farm and 13 Field Units in Virginia 1973-74 (Box-folder 58:13)
    - Report of the Virginia State Crime Commission 1967 (Box-folder 59:1)
    - Report of the Virginia State Crime Commission 1969, 1970, 1971, 1972, 1973 (Box-folder 59:2)
    - Report of the Virginia State Crime Commission 1973 and 1974 (Box-folder 59:3)
    - Report of the Virginia State Crime Commission 1975 and 1976 (Box-folder 59:4)
    - Reports 1971-72 (Box-folder 59:5)
    - Reports 1973 (Box-folder 59:6)
    - Report of the Private Security Industry Task Force 1974 (Box-folder 59:7)
    - Statistics, Data-General 1970 (Box-folder 59:8)
    - Roster and Appointments 1966-1970, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 59:9)
    - Virginia State Crime Commission Reports 1976 (Box-folder 59:10)
    - Virginia State Crime Commission Report on Shoplifting 1975 (Box-folder 59:11)
  - Divisions 1973 to 1975
    Pertains to the divisions of the Virginia State Crime Commission, as well as other criminal investigation divisions (both state and federal).
    - Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries 1974 (Box-folder 59:12)
    - Division of Investigation 1973-1974 (Box-folder 59:13)
    - Division of Justice and Crime Prevention 1974-1975 (Box-folder 59:14)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation undated (Box-folder 59:15)
    - Special Study Unit 1973-1974 (Box-folder 60:1)
    - Statutory Research and Drafting undated (Box-folder 60:2)
  - Drugs/Alcohol 1971 to 1981
    Pertains to drug and alcohol addiction, which was a main issue of the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - Addiction-Articles 1972-1973 (Box-folder 60:3)
    - Correctional Institution-Methadone Treatment for Addicts 1971-1972 (Box-folder 60:4)
    - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control I undated (Box-folder 60:5)
    - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control II undated (Box-folder 60:6)
    - Drug Abuse Advisory Council 1973-1976 (Box-folder 60:7)
    - Drug Abuse and Control undated (Box-folder 60:8)
    - Drug Abuse-Teenagers undated (Box-folder 60:9)
    - Marijuana Laws, Virginians for Study of, Roy B. Scherer, Executive Director 1973 (Box-folder 60:10)
    - NAACP: Drug Abuse 1972 (Box-folder 60:11)
    - Narcotics and Dangerous Drug Squad-Annual Report 1971 (Box-folder 60:12)
    - Narcotics and Drug Abuse Control, Governor’s Council 1972 (Box-folder 60:13)
    - Report of the Subcommittee to Study the Public Inebriate 1981 (Box-folder 60:14)
    - Rubicon-Door 1972-1974 (Box-folder 60:15)
    - Snug Harbour Hall, Inc. 1975 (Box-folder 60:16)
    - United Drug Abuse Council 1975 (Box-folder 60:17)
  - Gambling/Lottery
    Pertains to the gambling and lottery issues within Virginia.
    - Gambling/Lottery undated (Box-folder 60:18)
  - Institutions 1972 to 1979
    Pertains to the various types of correctional facilities within Virginia. Deals with the issues concerned with these facilities, as well as visits to correctional facilities in other states.
    - Assessment of Work Release and Related Furlough Programs 1975 (Box-folder 60:19)
    - Correctional Institution: Disturbances 1972 (Box-folder 60:20)
    - Early Release 1979 (Box-folder 60:21)
    - Escapees 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60:22)
    - Evaluation of the Rehabilitative School Authority and its Educational Functions 1976 (Box-folder 60:23)
    - First Report on Corrections-Virginia State Penitentiary 1973 (Box-folder 60:24)
    - Green Springs 1974 (Box-folder 61:1)
    - Incarceration in Virginia 1982 (Box-folder 61:2)
    - Inmate Complaints, Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61:3)
    - Inmate Violence 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61:4)
    - Dallas C. McWaters Jr., Case of 1974-1976 (Box-folder 61:5)
    - Press Releases/Statements-re. Prisons undated (Box-folder 61:6)
    - Prisons/Crime 1972 (Box-folder 61:7)
    - Phase IV Report-Study of Corrections 1975 (Box-folder 61:8)
    - Selected Probation and Parole Issues in Virginia 1980 (Box-folder 61:9)
    - Summary of Studies on the Correctional System undated (Box-folder 61:10)
    - Visit-Florida February 28-March 3, 1973 (Box-folder 61:11)
    - Visit-Wisconsin 1973 and 1974 (Box-folder 61:12)
    - Visits-Various undated (Box-folder 61:13)
    - Welfare and Institutions, Department of 1969 (Box-folder 61:14)
  - Investigations 1973 to 1975
    Pertains to investigations conducted with or on the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - American Civil Liberties Union undated (Box-folder 61:15)
    - Federal Communications Commission 1975 (Box-folder 61:16)
    - Portsmouth Probe 1973 (Box-folder 61:17)
  - Juvenile Crime 1972 to 1982
    Pertains to the issue of juvenile crime, which, the Virginia State Crime Commission dealt with on a continual basis.
    - Beaumont School for Boys 1973 (Box-folder 62:1)
    - Children and Youth in Trouble in Virginia 1977 (Box-folder 62:2)
    - Children and Youth in Trouble in Virginia, Phase II 1979 (Box-folder 62:3)
    - Comprehensive Long Range Master Plan for Juvenile and Youthful Offender Justice Systems 1974 (Box-folder 62:4)
    - Compulsory School Education-SJR 60 1974 (Box-folder 62:5)
    - Compulsory School Education-SJR 60: Report 1975 (Box-folder 62:6)
    - Juvenile Crime-Prevention undated (Box-folder 62:7)
    - Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court-Norfolk, VA undated (Box-folder 62:8)
    - National Council on Crime and Delinquency 1972-1973 (Box-folder 62:9)
    - Pendleton Project undated (Box-folder 62:10)
    - Pilot Cities Program 1973-1975 (Box-folder 62:11)
    - Services to Youthful Offenders Study-SJR 56 1972 (Box-folder 62:12)
    - The 286 Judicial Placements Program 1982 (Box-folder 62:13)
    - Virginia’s Schools: A Safe Environment? 1982 (Box-folder 62:14)
  - Legislation 1971 to 1992
    Pertains to legislation regarding the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - Legislation I undated (Box-folder 63:1)
    - Legislation II undated (Box-folder 63:2)
    - Legislation III undated (Box-folder 63:3)
    - Parole Abolition undated (Box-folder 63:4)
    - Senate Bill 187 of 1992, Gradual Release Initiative 1992 (Box-folder 63:5)
    - Vehicle Seizure Laws 1973 (Box-folder 63:6)
    - Watchmakers Licensing Law 1971-1974 (Box-folder 63:7)
  - Media 1971 to 1974
    Pertains to new releases and communication between the media and the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - Media-Correspondence 1971-1974 (Box-folder 63:8)
    - News Releases 1971-1973 (Box-folder 63:9)
  - Meetings 1971 to 1973
    Pertains to meetings of the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - Meetings 1971-1973 (Box-folder 63:10)
  - Pari-Mutuel Betting
    Pertains to issue of the pari-mutuel betting, which was a great source of debate within the state of Virginia.
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting I undated (Box-folder 63:11)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting II undated (Box-folder 63:12)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting III undated (Box-folder 64:1)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting IV undated (Box-folder 64:2)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting V undated (Box-folder 64:3)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting VI undated (Box-folder 64:4)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting VII undated (Box-folder 64:5)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting VIII undated (Box-folder 64:6)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting IX undated (Box-folder 64:7)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting X undated (Box-folder 64:8)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting XI undated (Box-folder 65:1)
    - Virginia State Crime Commission Report on Organized Crime on Pari-Mutuel Wagering on Horse Racing undated (Box-folder 65:2)
  - Personnel 1973
    Pertains to personnel within the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - Executive Director (Lewis W. Hurst) 1973 (Box-folder 65:3)
    - Staff undated (Box-folder 65:4)
  - Police 1968 to 1980
    Pertains to law enforcement personnel within Virginia.
    - Law Enforcement Officers Training Standards Commission 1972 (Box-folder 65:5)
    - Navy/Military Police 1975 (Box-folder 65:6)
    - Norfolk International Terminals –Police undated (Box-folder 65:7)
    - Pay Scale? 1978 (Box-folder 65:8)
    - Police Assistance Foundation, Inc. 1968-1969 (Box-folder 65:9)
    - Police Chiefs 1974-1975 (Box-folder 65:10)
    - Report on Law Enforcement Training 1980 (Box-folder 65:11)
    - Sheriffs undated (Box-folder 65:12)
    - Virginia State Troopers undated (Box-folder 65:13)
  - Sex Crimes 1973
    Pertains to the issue of sex crimes that consisted of abuse, rape, and pornography. This was a strong issue that the Virginia State Crime Commission, dealt with.
    - Pornography/Obscenity 1973 (Box-folder 65:14)
    - Sex Crimes Committee I undated (Box-folder 65:15)
    - Sex Crimes Committee II undated (Box-folder 65:16)
    - Sexual Assault Study 1976 (Box-folder 66:1)
    - Sexual Assault 1979 and 1981 (Box-folder 66:2)
  - Electronic Surveillance undated
    Pertains to the issue of electronic surveillance.
    - Electronic Surveillance-SB 367 undated (Box-folder 66:3)
  - Miscellaneous 1966 to 1976
    Pertains to miscellaneous issues/items within the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - Bulletproof Vest Pamphlet undated (Box-folder 66:4)
    - Federal Crime Insurance 1975-1976 (Box-folder 66:5)
    - Film: What Have You Got to Loose? 1973 (Box-folder 66:6)
    - Offender Aid and Restoration (OAR) undated (Box-folder 66:7)
    - Handbook for Virginia Grand Jurors 1976 (Box-folder 66:8)
    - Proposed film for the Virginia State Crime Commission 1973 (Box-folder 66:9)
    - Speedy Trial Act 1974 (Box-folder 66:10)
    - Travel Expenses 1966-1967 (Box-folder 66:11)
    - Vouchers 1971-1972 (Box-folder 66:12)
- Political Files 1959 to 2000
  Consists of papers relating to political issues within the state of Virginia, as well as the city of Norfolk. The series also contains papers and oversize items, involving Walker’s political campaigns.
  - City of Norfolk 1959
    Contains information in regard to the Norfolk City School Board, in which Walker was made a member in 1959.
    - Norfolk City School Board 1959 (Box-folder 67:1)
  - Elections 1950s, 1960s, 1970s, and 1990s.
    Contains information in regard to the campaigns that Walker was a part of.
    - Election Materials undated (Box-folder 67:2)
    - Election Materials/Platforms 1950s-1960s (Box-folder 67:3)
    - Primary and Election Results 1963-1974 (Box-folder 67:4)
    - Democratic Primary 1963- (Box-folder 67:5)
    - Primary Campaign and Election I 1965 (Box-folder 67:6)
    - Primary Campaign and Election II 1965 (Box-folder 67:7)
    - Spong Campaign 1966-Editorials, etc. I 1966 (Box-folder 67:8)
    - Spong Campaign 1966-Editorials, etc. II 1966 (Box-folder 67:9)
    - Spong Campaign 1966-Election Returns, 1966-Primary and General Election 1966 (Box-folder 67:10)
    - Spong Campaign 1966-Financial Data 1966 (Box-folder 67:11)
    - Spong Campaign 1966-Insurance 1966 (Box-folder 67:12)
    - Spong Campaign 1966-Letters of Appreciation and Materials 1966 (Box-folder 68:1)
    - Spong Campaign 1966-News Releases 1966 (Box-folder 68:2)
    - Spong Campaign 1966-Norfolk 1966 (Box-folder 68:3)
    - Spong Campaign 1966-Public Relations Committee-Press Releases 1966 (Box-folder 68:4)
    - Spong Campaign 1966-Schedule and Materials 1966 (Box-folder 68:5)
    - Walker Campaign 1967-Advertising 1967 (Box-folder 68:6)
    - Walker Campaign 1967-Financial Data 1967 (Box-folder 68:7)
    - Walker Campaign 1967-Information File 1967 (Box-folder 68:8)
    - Walker Campaign 1967-Letters (April 5-May 29) April 5-May 29, 1967 (Box-folder 68:9)
    - Walker Campaign 1967-Letters (June 5-August 21) June 5-August 21, 1967 (Box-folder 68:10)
    - Walker Campaign 1967-Letters August 22-31, 1967 (Box-folder 69:1)
    - Walker Campaign 1967-Letters September 5-November 21, 1967 (Box-folder 69:2)
    - Walker Campaign 1967-Petitions: Primary 1967 (Box-folder 69:3)
    - Walker Campaign 1967-Poster, re. Norfolk Headquarters at Janaf 1967 (Box-folder 69:4)
    - Walker Campaign 1967-Progress 7 Team: Advertising 1967 (Box-folder 69:5)
    - Rixey Campaign, 1968-Organization, Members, Etc. I 1968 (Box-folder 69:6)
    - Rixey Campaign, 1968-Organization, Members, Etc. II 1968 (Box-folder 69:7)
    - Battle Campaign I 1969 (Box-folder 69:8)
    - Battle Campaign II 1969 (Box-folder 69:9)
    - Democratic Primary Campaign, 1969-Letters 1969 (Box-folder 69:10)
    - Democratic Primary Campaign, 1969-Materials 1969 (Box-folder 69:11)
    - Democratic Primary Campaign, 1969-News Releases 1969 (Box-folder 70:1)
    - Democratic Primary Campaign, 1969-Poll Manning 1969 (Box-folder 70:2)
    - Duval Campaign 1970 (Box-folder 70:3)
    - Fitzpatrick Campaign 1970 (Box-folder 70:4)
    - Spong Campaign 1972-Correspondence and Letters of Appreciation 1972 (Box-folder 70:5)
    - Spong Campaign 1972-Editorials, Releases 1972 (Box-folder 70:6)
    - Spong Campaign 1972-Organization, Financial Data, etc. 1972 (Box-folder 70:7)
    - Walker Campaign 1975 (Box-folder 70:8)
    - Walker Campaign 1975-Candidate Questioning Data 1975 (Box-folder 70:9)
    - Walker Campaign 1975-Questionnaires 1975 (Box-folder 70:10)
    - Election 1979 (Box-folder 71:1)
    - Campaign 1995 (Box-folder 71:2)
    - Stanley Walker Campaign Materials 1990s-2000 (Box-folder 71:3)
    - Copies: candidate endorsements (surveys/questionnaires) 1999 (Box-folder 71:4)
  - People 1965 to 1993
    Pertains to the people that Walker dealt with while in the General Assembly, as well as in political campaigns.
    - Press Release: John Dalton undated (Box-folder 71:5)
    - Inaugural Information: Mills E. Godwin, Jr. 1965 (Box-folder 71:6)
    - Appointment of Senator Elmon T. Gray to Senate Ethics Advisory Panel January 13, 1993 (Box-folder 71:7)
    - Black Judge: William T. Mason 1976 (Box-folder 71:8)
    - Nick Rerras undated (Box-folder 71:9)
    - William Spong I undated (Box-folder 71:10)
    - William Spong II undated (Box-folder 71:11)
    - Elizabeth (Liz) Tate undated (Box-folder 71:12)
    - Albert Teich-Bills Introduced While in House 1972-1973 (Box-folder 71:13)
    - Stanley C. Walker: Biographical Information undated (Box-folder 71:14)
    - Stanley C. Walker: Reports undated (Box-folder 71:15)
  - Miscellaneous 1972 to 1987
    Pertains to miscellaneous political issues.
    - Student Legal Forum at University of Virginia/Joseph A. Jordan, Jr./Ian Smith/Arthur Ashe 1972 (Box-folder 71:16)
    - Virginian Pilot/Corbell Jones March 31,1987 (Box-folder 71:17)
- Speeches 1950s to 2000
  Consists of speeches that Walker and others made in regards to campaigns and issues within the state of Virginia.
  - Speeches undated (Box-folder 72:1)
  - Speeches 1950s-1960s (Box-folder 72:2)
  - Speeches 1963 (Box-folder 72:3)
  - Speeches 1964 (Box-folder 72:4)
  - Speeches 1965 (Box-folder 72:5)
  - Speeches 1966 (Box-folder 72:6)
  - Speeches I 1967 (Box-folder 72:7)
  - Speeches II 1967 (Box-folder 72:8)
  - Speeches III 1967 (Box-folder 72:9)
  - Speeches IV 1967 (Box-folder 72:10)
  - Speeches I 1968 (Box-folder 73:1)
  - Speeches II 1968 (Box-folder 73:2)
  - Speeches 1969 (Box-folder 73:3)
  - Speeches 1970 (Box-folder 73:4)
  - Speeches 1971 (Box-folder 73:5)
  - Speeches I 1972 (Box-folder 73:6)
  - Speeches II 1972 (Box-folder 73:7)
  - Speeches 1973 (Box-folder 73:8)
  - Speeches 1974 (Box-folder 73:9)
  - Speeches 1975 (Box-folder 73:10)
  - Speeches 1990s-2000 (Box-folder 73:11)
- Clippings 1959 to 2000
  Consists of clippings that Walker collected in regard to issues within the state of Virginia. Issues include of elections, crime, education, gambling, and the General Assembly.
  - Clippings 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 74:1)
  - City of Norfolk undated (Box-folder 74:2)
  - Crime Related undated (Box-folder 74:3)
  - Day Care undated (Box-folder 74:4)
  - Education undated (Box-folder 74:5)
  - Elections 1960s (Box-folder 74:6)
  - Election-1975 Campaign 1975 (Box-folder 74:7)
  - Election 1990s-2000 (Box-folder 74:8)
  - Gambling/Lottery undated (Box-folder 74:9)
  - General Assembly undated (Box-folder 74:10)
  - Health undated (Box-folder 74:11)
  - Labor undated (Box-folder 74:12)
  - Norfolk-Ledger Dispatch: Front Page June 30, 1959 (Box-folder 74:13)
  - Pari-Mutuel Betting undated (Box-folder 74:14)
  - Physical/Mental Health undated (Box-folder 74:15)
  - Political undated (Box-folder 74:16)
  - William Spong-Clippings I 1972 (Box-folder 74:17)
  - William Spong-Clippings II 1972 (Box-folder 75:1)
  - Tax/Revenue undated (Box-folder 75:2)
  - Transportation undated (Box-folder 75:3)
  - Virginia Pilot/Ledger Star-Sunday Commentary Section April 26, 1987 (Box-folder 75:4)
  - Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 75:5)
- Scrapbooks 1957 to 1997
  Consists of articles and miscellaneous items that Walker meticulously collected over the years in regard to issues within the state of Virginia, as well as personal interests.
  - Scrapbook I 1957-1963 (Box-folder 76:1)
  - Scrapbook II 1957-1963 (Box-folder 76:2)
  - Scrapbook I 1964-1965 (Box-folder 76:3)
  - Scrapbook II 1964-1965 (Box-folder 76:4)
  - Scrapbook 1965-1975 (Box-folder 76:5)
  - Scrapbook 1966-1975 (Box-folder 77:1)
  - Scrapbook 1968-1971 (Box-folder 77:2)
  - Scrapbook I 1971-1977 (Box-folder 77:3)
  - Scrapbook II 1971-1977 (Box-folder 77:4)
  - Scrapbook I 1972-1974 (Box-folder 78:1)
  - Scrapbook II 1972-1974 (Box-folder 78:2)
  - Scrapbook 1974-1976 (Box-folder 78:3)
  - Scrapbook 1976-1978 (Box-folder 78:4)
  - Scrapbook 1979-1980 (Box-folder 78:5)
  - Scrapbook 1980-1985 (Box-folder 79:1)
  - Scrapbook I 1986-1991 (Box-folder 79:2)
  - Scrapbook II 1986-1991 (Box-folder 79:3)
  - Scrapbook 1990-1996 (Box-folder 79:4)
  - Scrapbook 1996-1997 (Box-folder 79:5)
- Miscellaneous 1966 to 1999
  Consists of miscellaneous items that Walker had over the years. The items include appointment calendars, a diary, forms, programs, business cards, various documents and articles, notes, and maps.
  - Alice M. Harrison v. Mary Lou Lamme undated (Box-folder 80:1)
  - Annual Report of Dick Hux, Second Vice President 1966-1967 (Box-folder 80:2)
  - Appointment Calendars 1969 (Box-folder 80:3)
  - "Be a Good Guy"-buttons from "Your Friendly Miami Police Department" undated (Box-folder 80:4)
  - Business Card: Jim Fulmer, Secretary/Business Manager undated (Box-folder 80:5)
  - Business Card: Stanley C. Walker: President Pro Tempore undated (Box-folder 80:6)
  - Court Summons and Travel Expense Reimbursement Voucher 1975 (Box-folder 80:7)
  - Denial or Abridgement of Right to Work undated (Box-folder 80:8)
  - Department of Rehabilitative Services: Pamphlets 1988-1989 (Box-folder 80:9)
  - Diary 1973 (Box-folder 80:10)
  - Federal Energy Office Form undated (Box-folder 80:11)
  - Miscellaneous Financial undated (Box-folder 80:12)
  - Instructions of Interest Regarding Retirement and Group Life Insurance undated (Box-folder 80:13)
  - Lexington Tower 1972 (Box-folder 80:14)
  - "Memories for You"-1999 Calendar 1999 (Box-folder 80:15)
  - Monthly Minder 1972 (Box-folder 80:16)
  - NASA: Special Review Program-Technology in the Service of Man October 3, 1974 (Box-folder 80:17)
  - Norfolk City Democratic Committee Dinner Honoring the Honorable Thomas W. Moss, Jr. April 29, 1995 (Box-folder 80:18)
  - Norfolk Executive Club undated (Box-folder 80:19)
  - Norfolk Forum 1972-1973 (Box-folder 80:20)
  - Notebook and Notes undated (Box-folder 80:21)
  - Phyllis Schlafly Report (Vietnam) March and June 1975 (Box-folder 80:22)
  - Photo: Bill Deal and Ammon Tharp undated (Box-folder 80:23)
  - Photos: Unidentified undated (Box-folder 80:24)
  - Poe Museum undated (Box-folder 80:25)
  - Session Expenses 1968 (Box-folder 80:26)
  - 28th Annual Meeting: Association of Commonwealth’s Attorneys of Virginia undated (Box-folder 80:27)
  - U.S. Senate Joint Resolution 32 undated (Box-folder 80:28)
  - Virginia Municipal Review March 1969 (Box-folder 80:29)
  - "Virginians for Clinton/Gore 92’"- Bumper Sticker undated (Box-folder 80:30)
  - William and Mary Law Review-Vol. 10, #2 Winter 1968 (Box-folder 80:31)
- Oversize Items Located in Map Case 1965 to 1969
  - Map - "Election Districts, Street and Vicinity Guide, City of Virginia Beach, Virginia, City Planning Commission, Approved by Council, December 22, 1969" December 22, 1969
  - Oversize Poster - "General Election, City of Norfolk, Virginia, Tuesday, November 5, 1968: Directions for Voting" November 5, 1968
  - Map - "Fairfax County Virginia, Planning Division, 1965" 1965
  - Map - "Survey Showing Parcel of Property Located Within the Present Right-of-Way Limits of State Route #104 for W. Kenton Cason and Adella Page Cason" undated